-It is possible that an accident during start-up...
...of the particle accelerator has had consequences...
...incalculable. If so, then surely,
the Earth will be different. -There it is.
-Maybe we're not the only ones who survived the storm.
What is this, Ricardo? - A video camera.
-Over there, in the background. -But who was recording this?
-And why didn't they respond to our signals? And where did they go?
-The device is a kind of transponder,
It is used to send a signal indicating our position.
- Are you sending a signal? To whom?
-I don't know. -It's not just for broadcasting...
...long-distance signals, but also to receive them.
What do you want me to do now? - Forget what you did.
Whatever happens, not a single word to the captain.
-Do you want to be my wife? -Yes.
-Well, I now pronounce us husband and wife.
What is the cancer? - It's prostate cancer,
But they're just markers. I can only give you this.
-Do me a favor, doctor? Don't tell anyone.
-Constantly deceiving yourself to convince yourself that you're not...
...in love, it must be exhausting, right?
...straight to the bottom.
-I'm sure you don't give a shit about Ainhoa, you're fighting for something else.
-Last warning, I'm nobody to you.
You're right about us not knowing each other,
Because no one lets me. - You're a fucking murderer...
...and you won't get out of here. -Hey!
-A life raft is missing. -Gamboa!
Who are you? - Why don't you ask Julia?
-What does Julia have to do with all this?
-Do you know anything about her, about her life, about who she is?
-What was that?
-Where's Gamboa? -We only found Ulises.
-It can't be. -What will happen to Julia?
-Whatever happens, it won't be your fault, it will be mine.
-We demand that Ulises be tried for the murder of Gamboa.
-Sorry, I made a mistake. -Yes.
-Captain, we've found Gamboa.
(Sound) (JOKE) -It's a cell phone.
-It is impossible for the raft to overtake the boat,
I need to talk to him. -No, he's my patient, Captain.
-You can go, but if you want to be by my side,
You'll have to play by my rules. I told you I wouldn't lie to you, Ramiro,
but there are things I can't tell you.
-What's that? -It's been on for three hours...
...on a loop, it might be coming from the ship we're heading towards.
-Ainhoa ​​is now with Ulises. -Next time,
I will kill him and your father; and, of course, your sister.
"Julia's cheating on us, I don't like it." "What are you doing here?"
Why did you come back? - Don't ask what you already know, Julia.
Do your duty. -There are more signs,
They are bombarding the ship with signals.
(Sign) Yes, tell me.
-Ulises, I was wrong. Gamboa's back and...
I don't love you, Ulysses, I don't love you. -Captain, everyone,
Go up to the bridge, they're calling us on the phone.
They're calling us! -Captain.
(Interferences)
Captain!
Captain, are you there? Can you hear me? - I can hear you.
-Thank God, Captain. This is Commander Hopkins speaking.
We need to be rescued, we have four hours left to live.
-We'll be there as soon as possible, give us your position.
-Our position won't be of much use to them, Captain,
We are 367 km from your ship, on its vertical axis.
-Above.
-We are Commander Hopkins, Engineer Davis,
and Dr. Kolivanov. We're speaking to you from the space station...
...international. -What are you telling us? Are you astronauts?
-Fleet.
"The first day of school, after the holidays,
you met your friends again.
Some had grown their hair, others had lost it...
...some teeth, and others were higher than before the summer.
But besides your friends, there were always new kids...
...who came from other schools. At first, you didn't recognize them...
...you're welcome, but after playing with them at recess,
They were your friends just like the others."
-How long have you been up there? -Haven't you been able to see anything?
-Are there more people alive?
-Do you see Earth? -Didn't even Houston answer?
-Bubble, go outside. "Because as my mom used to say,
the important thing is to make new friends,
wherever they come from."
-It hurts a little, right?
-It's healthy. -I'm not talking about exercise,
I'm talking about the fact that you're no longer with Ulysses, that he left you.
Julia, I'm with you, on your team. Now you see me happy...
...because I'm with Julian, but if we play how many times...
...they've planted more on you, you can't beat me.
-We are not alone! We are not alone!
The signals are on TV, they were spacemen.
The captain talks to them.
You have to prepare a fish soup or a crab cream for them.
Because in space the food is very bad.
What's up? Don't you want the astronauts to come?
-What kind of cloud are those?
-Let's see, Commander. -We all have questions,
But let's take it one step at a time. -If we all speak at once,
we're not going to understand each other, okay?
-Captain, we need more information.
-Tell us, Commander. -We're in a critical situation.
The Zvezda and three life support modules have left...
...to generate oxygen, we have an evacuation vessel.
In three hours and four minutes we will undock,
and in 45 minutes we will land five miles from your position.
-Let's see, Commander. We're sailors.
We're not used to your jargon. Please be clearer.
-It's simple, when we fall into the sea, or we are rescued...
...in 30 minutes or we'll sink.
-I give you my word that we will rescue him.
-Thank you. You don't know what this is like. We had lost hope.
We thought we were dead. (SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN)
-Commander, do you see land? We know of an island,
of about 3,000 hectares, south of the Azores,
but we do not know their exact situation.
-The display system was managed from Houston and,
To see land with the naked eye, it should have a surface...
...the size of Nebraska.
Captain, can we talk?
Alone. -Yes, of course.
-Well, gentlemen, you heard him. Everyone back to work. Let's go!
Let's see, they are the first human beings we have encountered.
Damn! That's why no. I'll tell you what they'll do.
Ramiro, rearrange a cabin. The others take care of it...
...to organize a party all together, okay?
But I want a big party. Banners, garlands!
Whatever it takes. As if there were no tomorrow.
Let these people not think that we don't know how to receive visitors!
Gamboa, this is for you too. Piti, you're supposed to be...
...the professional at this. -Yes, man!
-Well, I want to see it. -Let's go, officer, let's go.
-A space capsule falling from the sky and a training ship...
...lost and out of fuel. I wouldn't bother preparing...
...a cabin for those guys.
I don't think it will turn out well, what a shame.
Ramiro, I want you at the winery in 30 minutes.
I need you to connect me to the transponder.
-Yeah. And I need answers. -No, you need answers.
And how many answers do you need?
Do three seem enough to you?
Three questions, three answers. Not one more.
So choose wisely. - Are you serious?
-Strange way to waste the first one. Answer:
Yes, I'm serious. I was joking.
First question.
-Is Pilar dead?
I need to know.
-Dead and buried under tons of tectonic mass and millions...
...of cubic liters of water.
I thought you were smarter, Ramiro.
Think better about the second one.
30 minutes and in wineries.
-We must put the boat hooks in the bow!
Let's go!
And set the nets!
Let's go fishing for spacemen!
Come on, we need more networks! Come on, all the ones there are! Let's go!
-Let's go see in the cellar, let's go.
-Just a second, please. Ainhoa, please give me a second.
75 meters in length and four decks give much more...
...than it seems.
If we follow the quadrants to the letter, we won't see each other...
...the faces here.
I'll shower from eight thirty to a quarter to nine,
you from nine fifteen to nine thirty.
Lunch, dinner, and breakfast shifts: me first...
...and you're third. -Please...
-Outings on deck. You, Monday, Wednesday, and Friday.
Me, Tuesdays, Thursdays, Saturdays and alternate Sundays.
Regarding homework, I'll talk to my father about it...
...get us something.
Take.
Now that I think about it, I think these quadrants won't be necessary.
Do you know why?
-No.
-Because no one wakes up in the morning loving someone...
...and stops loving him at nap time.
I was down there for 18 minutes, just 18.
Nobody stops loving someone in 18 minutes Ainhoa.
I don't care what you tell me,
I know you still love me.
(Beep) - Do you see us now, Commander?
-No.
-He's my trusted man. Whatever he can tell me,
You can tell him about it. -Two things.
Four days after the cataclysm, between 16:03 and 16:19,
Washington time, we received six satellite broadcasts.
(SPEAKS IN ENGLISH) -One of them is his ship.
-That's when the warehouse's transponder was activated.
But if there were five more signals, could there be another five ships?
-We don't know if they were ships. We sent them the coordinates.
(SPEAKS IN ENGLISH) Since that day, we have issued...
...SOS signals and the film to attract attention.
We have only managed to contact you.
-Are you okay? -Yes, fine.
"Are you all right, Captain?" "Yes. And the second thing that..."
...you wanted to tell us? - A stormy mass with clouds...
...of vertical development and electric charge...
...approaching you. Clouds over 100 knots...
...and winds of 170 km/h. The vortex is 47 miles away...
...from his position, but he moves forward quickly.
They'll have it on them within four hours.
-Right at the time of the rescue. -We can't delay the evacuation.
I know what I'm asking for is suicide, but my obligation is...
...try to save the lives of my men.
I will understand any decision you make.
We will get back to you in two hours.
-Okay, Commander.
-Cuckoo! -Tomato juice?
-Almost a Bloody Mary. The Salomé Method for heartbreak. Drink.
"Salomé, I don't need to get drunk. This isn't the first time I've been dumped."
-You're lying. They've never let you go in your life. It's written all over you...
...in the freckle above your eyebrow.
On the other hand, I have seven boyfriends and all seven have left me.
You, baby.
-Come on.
How delicious, please!
Where did you learn to do it? - Alejandro Medino, 2001-2003.
Hairdresser, an artist with scissors and a cocktail shaker.
-And what happened? -Barbara, shampoo saleswoman.
Bust: 105; operated. A bitch. - Did he cheat on you?
-Right down to the stem. But once that bitch came to get her hair cut,
I traded his shampoo for glue. Didn't you want to be together?
Come on, inseparable ones. Drink. - What?
-Grandma.
-The difference is that the one who took my boyfriend away from me...
...she's not a shampoo commercial, she's the captain's daughter.
And she's no bitch, she's a sweetheart.
-And that doesn't help, right?
-Salomé, I'm even more devastated after two weeks...
...what I've been through with Ulysses, for eight years...
...that I've been with Philipe. I feel like a really bad person.
-At the end of the world everything is magnified more.
One day here is more than a year ago.
Everything hurts more, that's why you feel worse. Drink.
I want you to think positively and brighten up that face,
Because one nail drives out another. And astronauts...
...they're going to come looking for a party. Yes, because as far as I know,
Up there, there are no sluts. (THEY LAUGH)
Come on, cheers.
-I've seen you before with Ulysses.
-I haven't spoken to him, really.
I haven't even looked at him.
-It was a lie, I hadn't seen you;
but whenever you do, I'll end up knowing.
And I hope you are clear about the terms of our contract.
If you're with Ulysses, I'll kill him, your father, and your sister.
Himself.
-Come on, get it all out, quick.
-25 years of logbooks. Never the Estrella...
...has faced a cyclone of this nature.
-We survived the cataclysm storm.
-That storm only grazed us. The cyclone will hit us full on.
Ricardo, there's no land. The cyclones are no longer losing strength;
On the contrary, they become stronger and stronger.
And we're without an engine. Without propulsion, we'll sink.
Under normal circumstances I would give both legs for astronauts,
but not the 42 lives on board.
-I gave them my word that we would save them.
-You've also given your word to the crew...
...that you'd keep them alive. How many words does a captain have?
-Always one more than a first officer.
We're not going to move from the coordinates, is that clear?
Order everyone to put on their vests.
Don't you hear me? I gave you an order, officer.
Stand at attention and obey my order.
Square up!
-Come on, guys. How's it going? -Is it straight?
-A little more to the left. -It has to look really nice.
-Vilma, Vilma!
I'm an idiot.
I know, an idiot capable of risking the paternity of your child...
...the dice, but I also know that when I'm around you...
I am better.
I told you I love you...
...and you didn't say anything, Vilma.
The question is simple:
(Noise) Do you love me?
-Don't know.
-This one, there it is. Come on. Start with your homework.
-What is mouse in English? -Mouse.
Like Mickey Mouse on TV. It's written like this:
M-O-U-S-E.
-If the TV owners are in heaven,
Are they... dead?
-No, honey, no. No one's dead here.
They are in a spaceship, which is...
It's like a hotel, but it's up in the sky.
-No, they're in a rocket. Like this.
And it is higher than the clouds.
They are very far away. -If they are in heaven,
maybe they've seen mom.
-I don't know, honey. Honestly, I don't think so.
Imagine there are a lot of people in heaven. It would be a coincidence, wouldn't it?
-Yes, that's true. There are many people in heaven.
There are more people than on the Gran Vía during the parade...
...of the Three Wise Men. -Look, let's make a deal.
You do your homework, and as soon as I speak...
...with the astronauts I ask them if they've seen Mom.
Okay? Come on.
(COMPLAINS) - It hurts. The same thing happened to me here.
12 stitches. I wanted to take the appendix home,
But the doctors wouldn't let me. They were unfriendly.
I have seen these points before.
I don't know where, but I've seen them.
-Is it connected? -Yes.
And now the second question: why us?
Why the hell are we alive? Is it for a reason or is it just a coincidence?
-Are you asking me if the crew...
...of the North Star we are a kind of chosen ones?
The answer is yes, we are chosen.
Almost everyone.
Now I need you to leave me alone.
-Very good.
-I love you.
-Julia, these guys have been in space for 170 days,
that are horny, that come with accumulated love.
(LAUGHS) - What? - As soon as you pout...
...to the commander, puts you into orbit before you tell him:
"My name is Ju...". (RÍE)
-We need to put on our vests. Is that alcohol?
-No no.
-Oh, no? -No.
-Can I join you? -This is a very exclusive club.
-Yes? -There's only one way in.
-Let's see, how? -When was the last time...
...that they rejected you like a stinker?
-Seven minutes, 43 seconds ago. -Fuck.
-I've declared my love to Vilma, she told me she doesn't know.
-Well, but then he might go and say yes,
So he's not in the club. -But what's he going to say?
That's the preamble to the ass kicking.
Now, that's what I get for renouncing my creed.
First, never be friends with an aunt, ever.
Second, if when you are with her you do not see the dust clearly,
stop listening to her or you might get attached to her.
And third, if you get attached to him, move to another city.
(LAUGHS) I have fallen with Vilma,
and look, it doesn't even turn me on, but here, I'm completely in love,
You know? Up to my neck. Turned into an asshole,
the father of all assholes. - You're not an asshole, Piti.
(IRONIC) -No, I'm not. -You're not an asshole.
-On the contrary, you're no longer an asshole.
I'm going to get more juice, because it seems to me...
...that the afternoon is going to be very long.
-Captain!
-Dime.
-I'm crazy about your daughter.
I'm screwed.
I love her, and she loves me.
Well, yesterday he loved me, today he says no.
I don't know what to do, I'm going crazy.
-Ulises, that's something between you and Ainhoa.
-Just a second, Captain, please. Give me a second.
I told her I didn't believe her, but I'm scared.
I'm afraid it's true.
You don't know anything, do you?
-Ulises,
People change their minds, you should know that better than anyone.
The doctor, do you remember?
One day you loved her and the next you didn't,
and now he walks like a zombie,
shattered.
(Thunder)
-Captain?
Captain!
Captain, what's wrong? Help! Help!
Please, I need help! -Ricardo! Ricardo!
No, Ricar...! -Doctor.
-Julia! Julia! -Captain!
-You have decided to return to the nest.
-Why Ulysses? Why him?
Tell me what I have to do!
I'm going to do it, whatever it is, it doesn't matter.
But let me be with him.
I love him.
-How much? How much do you love him?
Do you love him enough to take his life...
...to the man who is an obstacle to you being with him?
Do you love him enough to kill me?
-Yes.
-Miriam, a Bisbal fan, left me because she said...
...that we were going too slow for her.
(THEY LAUGH)
-Do you want a resume? -Yes.
-José Vicente, professor of Applied Physics,
elevator panic. (LAUGHS)
He left me because it turns out I reminded him of his daughter,
because I was the same age as her.
(THEY LAUGH) -Wait.
Inés, ugly, ugly... -Oh, poor thing.
-She left me for a guy who was missing an eye.
(LAUGHS) I swear.
-For Inés. -For Inés... and her boyfriend.
-Philipe. College sweethearts.
I always had to strain the orange juice...
...because he hated pulp.
He didn't leave me.
-Vilma.
We met her pregnant and I with a piece of gum on my forehead.
He's a thousand times better than any girl I've ever met. 1,000 times better.
He doesn't love me.
-¡Bah, bah!
-Julia, the captain.
The appendix area is as hard as a rock.
You have to operate on him. -What?
-Get in the shower. Come on, get in the shower.
-The appendix. -Yes, appendicitis. Come on, honey.
To the shower.
-If you love him so much, you just have to shoot...
...and then you throw the lamp on the floor,
you rip your shirt,
you cut your lip with the box cutter...
...and you say I tried to force myself on you.
You're the captain's daughter and I'm the bad boy on the ship.
It's impossible for them not to believe you.
If you love Ulysses so much, if you want to be with him so much,
a slight movement of your index finger and you'll get it.
You just have to shoot.
(CRIES)
-From the Block. -Yes.
-Clouds are like glitter. -Yeah.
-They seem to have little lights. "-Julian, can you hear me?"
-Yes, Salome, tell me.
-Listen carefully: Julia is going to operate on Ricardo.
-What? -Appendicitis.
-Fuck!
-But the worst of all is that he has never operated on anyone;
neither appendicitis nor anything.
Are you listening to me, Julian? - Yes, I can hear you.
-You are in command of the Star.
For God's sake!
(Coup)
-It's a horse mackerel. -Yes, I can see it.
What's that? What the fuck...?
(Blows)
But what's this about? Come on.
-What is that? -I don't know.
-It's raining horse mackerel.
It's because of the cyclone,
that takes sea water and spits it out hundreds of kilometers.
-The mother who gave birth to him.
-What's that?
Attention, new order. We hoist the gaff.
We turned 60 degrees to port.
It's an order, I repeat. -Very well, De la Cuadra.
-Sorry for the astronauts, but we're leaving. Let's go.
-Let's go.
(Radio in English)
(Beeps)
-What happened? -Calm down.
-What time is it? The commander and his crew...
-He's just been fainting. You have a serious case of appendicitis.
Julia is going to operate on you. Tell the doctor.
-We have a cyclone approaching the ship...
...and some men to rescue.
Tell Julia to operate on me later.
-Don't worry, Julian is in charge of the Estrella.
-But what the fuck...?
We are moving.
We are moving away from the coordinates.
-"An incision is made on the right side of the abdomen...
...leaving the blind man uncovered."
Julia, I'm sorry. I don't know why I kissed you.
-I had to.
I have to perform an operation for which I am not qualified...
...in the middle of a storm and incredibly drunk.
Lee.
-"The appendix is ​​removed, clamped, and tied at the base...
...and it cuts off." That must be why everything here is magnified.
You have created a complicity,
I thought it was very good and...
-Piti, protocol, please. Forget the kiss.
-"The stump is sewn, the cecum is introduced and the wound is saturated."
I don't need everything to be magnified to see...
...that you're hot, Julia.
You are good magnified,
without magnifying and in all ways, Julia.
Leo.
(Whistle)
-Ricardo, please don't take off the IV. Ricardo!
Please...
-"The suture that comes out can be made of loose stitches,
continuous or staples".
-Give me codeine so I can handle the pain. I can't have surgery.
I have to stop us from leaving, Salome.
-I'm not going to give you anything. -Give me codeine!
-Julia, are you okay?
Maybe you'd do well to eat something, some sautéed seaweed,
something to help you... Julia, are you okay?
-No. -No what?
-Look at you. You're going to kill yourself.
-Step aside, Salome.
-It would be handy to have a guide like this,
to tell you point by point how not to screw up in a relationship.
I would have done better with Vilma.
-Take it easy with Vilma.
I know your profile:
intelligent, rebellious, cunning.
If you overwhelm her, she runs away.
Like Ulysses.
Maybe if I hadn't pressured him...
Eh... Vale.
-Julia, I'll tell you something. -What?
-Everyone on this ship knew that Ulysses...
...he was in love with Ainhoa.
Except two people: you and him.
-Doctor.
The captain has regained consciousness.
(VIDEO) "Captain. Captain."
-Hello, Mr. Astronaut. I'm doing my homework.
Do you know how to say "bunny" in English?
-If you say "rabbit."
Who are you, "little girl"?
-Valeria. My dad is the captain of everyone.
Is it true that you are in heaven and that you see everything?
-Absolutely everything.
-Do you see my mom? She went to heaven a few months ago.
She's blonde like me, with hair here and very pretty.
Do you see her?
-The truth is that today everything is full of clouds.
But I will look for her.
-When you see her, tell her that I always finish my food,
that I lost a tooth and that I wet the bed,
But only for one day. And Dad likes it...
...a very pretty girl, but not as pretty as her.
-I'll tell her. -And that I miss her.
-Come with me!
I want the biggest one with a curl.
Tighten the foremast well to raise the lower topsail.
Okay? Let's go!
-Julian!
What the fuck are you doing? - Saving your own skin and everyone else's.
The wind doesn't push us enough,
we hoisted the mizzenmast fully.
-Give a new order right now, turn the Star around.
-You don't realize. It's raining fish, Ricardo.
This isn't a normal cyclone. If we don't leave, it'll swallow us up.
-I told you to turn the ship around.
-No, it would be suicide.
And there are too many people on this boat that I love.
If you have forgotten who you want on board,
I feel sorry for you, but I won't kill my own.
Oh...!
But what the fuck are you doing?
-Ah...!
Give the order, Julian. -No.
(SHOUTS)
-Have you had enough? We're leaving, damn it.
(SHOUTS) -Aaaaaah!
-Captain!
Captain, stop.
-Papi.
-Let me go.
Let me go.
-The man from heaven wants to talk to you.
-Tell me, commander.
-Captain, let's get on the ship.
We will undock from the station in 9 minutes.
In 33 minutes we will cross the atmosphere.
In 45 minutes we will land near your position.
-We'll be there, Commander.
-Captain, thank you.
The cyclone is more powerful than it seemed.
Over 600 km of storm mass and growing.
We're going to have a bad time for a while.
-It won't be the first time we've had a bad time.
Good flight, Commander.
Save the Star.
I'm going to have surgery.
Try not to let us move too much,
I don't want the doctor to cut the appendix that she shouldn't.
-Ricardo, we're doing the right thing.
It's either them or us.
-I know. It's always like this, one or the other.
-What do you think you're doing? -Well, the same as you.
I'm going to clean like an idiot...
...in the middle of a storm. -Yeah, but this is my turn.
-And mine. -That's a lie, it's Piti's.
-Yeah, but Piti got dizzy and couldn't clean...
...and vomit at the same time.
What happened? What's changed, Ainhoa?
Tell me, for God's sake. Tell me. Hey.
Is it because of something I've done, Ainhoa?
I know I can be a jerk sometimes, I know;
But I'll change. Tell me what's going on. Tell me.
I swear I'm going to change, Ainhoa.
Tell me.
-You can force me to clean with you,
but not to talk to you.
(Door)
-Forward.
-I have the third question. -Are you sure?
It's his last shot.
-If I were to confront you, if I were to jeopardize your plans,
would you kill me?
-I wouldn't hesitate for a second.
Where I come from, betrayal is paid for with death.
(English voices)
-What the hell are you doing, the crabs aren't hoisted?
I want the whole cloth unfolded, please!
-Where's Ricardo? I have to perform emergency surgery on him.
-He told me he was going to the infirmary. -Well, he didn't go.
Call him over the PA system.
At any time, your intestine can perforate.
-Ricardo, can you hear me?
(Whistle)
It is not possible.
The mother who... -What's wrong?
-Ricardo! Ricardo, can you hear me?
-Where are you going? -Outside.
You son of a bitch!
-Is it Ricardo? -Yes.
-What do you intend? -To rescue the astronauts alone.
-Hold me. -I think we should be...
...in the cabins. -No, man, no.
-Wake.
Well, yes. Yes. I'm going to say yes.
To Piti. I love him, I want to be with him.
(REMEMBER) "With Vilma, take it easy.
If you overwhelm her, she runs away."
-Well, turn 70 degrees, sailor. You've got it on the port side.
-Piti, what... I've already thought about it...
...and I already have an answer. -Vilma, leave it.
Don't pay attention to me, I'm crazy.
You know how this end of the world thing is,
everything is magnified. And I became magnified and confused.
You and I are friends, Vilma.
What am I supposed to be in love with you, it's absurd.
I'm sorry I put you in this predicament.
But that's it. A clean slate...
...and we start from scratch.
Look, if you can set me up with Estela,
let's see if the flame is rekindled,
You can name your baby after me, for example.
-Ricardo, contest!
Ricardo, damn it! Answer! I'm seeing you in the boat!
Turn around, damn it! Turn around, damn it!
You've got a typhoon blowing down your neck! Don't you realize?
At the first blow of the sea, you're going to go to hell!
Ricardo, for your mother's sake. You're in no condition to save anyone!
You have to have surgery, what the fuck!
You're going to faint before those people fall into the sea!
Ricardo, for the holy virgin's sake! Answer!
Answer me!
Answer me, damn it!
Ricardo, listen.
I have cancer.
-Let me go.
-What the hell are you talking about? -About the prostate.
Julia diagnosed me. I have some markers...
...I don't know what kind of milk. On land I could be called,
on the boat, not much.
-If a wave were to swallow us right now,
Is this all I would want?
Just this?
"Are you sure about that, Julian?" "I'm afraid so."
That's why I need you not to kill yourself.
Please. I won't be here forever,
but the people I love with all my soul, yes.
Ulysses, Salome. And you're going to have to take care of them, my friend.
-I don't love you.
-Julian. Julian, I'm so sorry. -Ricardo, don't be so sorry.
Stop rowing, I'm coming for you. What the fuck.
-And if those astronauts are so important to you,
we will go look for them,
Let's see if with a bit of luck they can handle playing mus.
-His fever is over 40, I have to operate on him now.
-The astronauts have fallen more than six miles from here.
-And the sea pushes them away. We need propulsion to get there.
What the fuck are we doing? (WALKIE) -"First Officer,
We lose them. Should we lower the mainsail further?
-No, or the wind will tear the sails. We have to lower them all.
-Lower all sail and keep visual contact with the ship.
-Without fuel we won't be able to rescue them.
-He's leaving us. We have to do something.
-Wait! Look, look...
Oars.
We have to build oars.
Mount an elevated structure in the dining room,
and put rowers using the portholes as hatches.
-Like in the "Vicky the Viking" cartoons.
-That's crazy!
-It might work. We need floorboards,
wooden crates... whatever, bunk beds. We only have ten minutes.
Ricardo, let's build those oars, damn it.
I'll take care of it. And I want to see you later, buddy, don't mess with me.
Acompáñale a la enfermería. -Ricardo, hay que operar. Vamos.
To the infirmary! - You guys, come with me!
We have a job to do!
-Come on, come on! -We'll play "where is it."
-Let's go.
-Come on, come on.
Come on, come on! -What's up?
-Here. -Come on, guys.
-Careful.
-First of all: make seats for each porthole.
First we use the tables, then you cross them, okay?
Come on, come on, damn it!
-Come on, come on!
-Come on, come on, come on!
-Are you guys okay? -Here.
-We'll make a seat over there. Another one over there too.
Well, without rushing. That's right, in order.
-Come on, come on, come on!
-Come on, let's go!
-Julia, how are you?
-GOOD.
-What's that? -Ricardo.
-Anesthesia. I'm going to sedate you. -No. Local anesthesia.
-I can't remove your appendix without local anesthesia.
-Yes, I can! I have to perform a rescue. The walkie.
-Salomé, I'm not going to do it with local anesthesia.
-Attention, they should put pillows in the portholes to...
...that they support the oars well, and that they cover them with rags...
...or whatever the mangoes are. -Yes, my friend!
Let's see, we use the pillows to protect the portholes!
I want the oar handles covered with rags!
I don't want them to get hurt!
Don't move the porthole guards!
Very good, you are doing very well!
Five more minutes and that's it!
-I'm going to operate on you by giving orders through the walkie!
-Yes, without any stress, as if you were in position.
Yes, you're going to do it. -Salomé, I can't.
I can't. -Look at my face.
Yes you can because we trust you, and you know how to do it;
him and me, and you're going to do it.
(Shouting)
-Nothing's wrong! Let's keep going!
-Okay, come on.
-Come on. Come on, honey.
-Ah!
Oh my God!
-Help!
(Noise) Ah!
Help!
Who are you? Let me go.
What do you want? Let me go! Let me go.
-Okay, let's get it on the floor. -Okay, little by little, okay?
-Careful, okay? -Come on, get those oars in the water!
-Calm down. Take a deep breath.
Okay, now tell me if you notice anything, okay?
Do you notice anything?
And now? -No.
-Go.
(WALKIE) -"Ricardo".
-The walkie, quick!
-Ricardo, calm down. -I'm listening.
-We have the whole setup in the dining room.
The ship is 7.5 miles away, and we are ready to row.
Shall we give them the order, captain?
-¡Remen!
-Bubble, conduct this orchestra for me!
And... two!
And... and... three!
-What are you doing? Are you crazy? Let me go. Let me go.
-In a matter of minutes my life will go to hell, Ainhoa;
So, yeah, I'm crazy.
(THEY SHOUT)
-Come on.
We continue.
-Go on!
-Come on! (THEY SHOUT)
A!
-Don't be afraid, doctor. I trust you.
Oh!
-Help me put the dividers on. They're there, grab them.
(THEY SHOUT)
-A!
-Ah!
Are you OK?
I can't find it. -Please.
-Wait.
I can't find it.
Salome, please bring me the book, I need to see it.
-Ah!
-What are you doing? I have to go.
(THEY SHOUT)
-Ten!
-Boys! -One!
-I remind you that we are not dancers,
we are sailors!
-Yes, I think I have it. -Yes?
(Whining)
-Salomé, the vacuum cleaner. We need more suction. Quickly.
Quick, put it on.
-I'm broken, Ainhoa.
You say you don't love me and I don't understand.
Make him understand. -Let me out.
-Convince me that you really don't love me.
I swear I'll disappear from your life forever, I swear.
-Salomé, you're losing a lot of blood. Gauze.
Soak the gauze.
-From the Block. -Captain!
-Ricardo, please. -Situation.
-Go.
-Three! (They shout)
-Again!
A!
-Ricardo, target five miles, five miles.
Damn, we have a cyclone right over our heads.
I've never seen anything like it in my life. The sea is coming in on our port side,
we have to compensate for the rowing.
-Help yourself with the rudder to compensate...
...and make sure the sea doesn't get in... from the side.
-I made a mistake.
I thought it was you, but I was wrong.
You were a whim,
a nonsense.
And I thought I could love you, but I couldn't.
-No me convences.
-If you say you love me,
leave me alone, I beg you.
Please leave me alone forever.
-Okay. I'll get away from you, but first I'm going to kiss you.
Kisses don't lie, Ainhoa.
It's just that, a kiss, nothing more.
-Go!
-Guys, one! (SCREAMING)
-We're going overboard. Starboard only. Bubble, can you hear me?
-Starboard only. Not you.
Ready...Go!
One! (SCREAMING)
Of the!
-I'm going to section the appendix.
-Okay. -I need you to clip it here, like this,
and don't let it go for anything in the world. -Good.
(THEY SHOUT)
-Vilma! -Vilma, are you okay?
-Yes. -Come on! Let's go!
One! (SCREAMING)
AND...
-Ricardo. Ricardo?
-Ricardo, we're two miles away. -Keep rowing.
-You heard the captain.
Keep rowing, for your fucking life.
Keep rowing, let's go!
-Don't come any closer. Stay still!
-We're at five boat lengths, one more effort, guys.
-That's it. -That's it.
-He's losing a lot of blood.
-Four lengths! That's it! That's it!
A few more strokes and we'll have them. That's it!
-Eh!
(Beeps)
-¿Ricardo?
-Two lengths! That's it!
-Ricardo! -You're going to help me lay a track.
We're going to give you a transfusion. - You?
-Yes, I'm a universal donor. There, where the syringes are.
-One boat! We're almost there!
-Put pressure on the wound. -With both hands?
-Yes, push him. Hard. -Run, baby, run.
Ricardo, please.
-And another one!
And another one.
And another one. Until the captain says something.
-Stop. Stop rowing. We've arrived, we've got them there.
Good job.
-Do you remember?
Just like our first date, huh?
-The show's over. We're getting ready to raise the ship,
okay? -Okay. Come on, Jose.
-Carefully, but also with shine.
-That's it?
Are we out of the cyclone yet? (STAMMERS) - No, it's the eye.
We are in the middle of the eye of the cyclone.
That's why it doesn't rain.
Isn't it beautiful?
-That's it.
Oh, sorry.
-You are forgiven.
And it has nothing to do with the fact that he just saved my life.
This is no time for apologies,
but I'm sorry I doubted you...
...and called her a liar.
-That's because I gave him my blood.
-Blood with a little bit of joy.
If the Civil Guard stops you, you break the breathalyzer.
-Did you operate on me while drunk? -No, drunkenness...
...it just passed me by, believe me.
-Well, the truth is that I've been high all day too.
-Don't come any closer, please.
Stop! Don't come any closer!
-You're going to have to shoot.
(CRYING) - Please don't come any closer. Please, I beg you.
Don't come any closer. -Fire that harpoon...
...it's the only way you can make me think you don't love me,
Ainhoa.
-Take it down carefully.
-Ah!
-Some more!
It's worth it, it's worth it!
-Ricardo, we have her.
-Get those men out of there right now.
-Guys, you open the hatch.
-Let's go.
(CRIES)
-What? -There's no one.
There's no one here, officer.
-Ricardo, the ship is empty.
They're not there. The astronauts aren't there.
(CRIES)
(ALL) - Here! Here!
-Please!
-We have seen hundreds of people die.
-He's saying he's willing to let those people die...
...20 meters from their boat. - They're also...
...survivors, Captain, just like us.
-It's algae!
(Noise) -Now!
Oh!
(SHOUTS) -Who were you talking to?
-Something is happening on the ship, but we don't know what it is.
-I'll do whatever you want. -Are you sure?
-Yes, please. I swear.
-It's an epidemic! We're going to die! -It's important that it doesn't spread.
-It's spreading throughout the ship.
-They could have anthrax, chickenpox, hemorrhagic fever...
Most of them are fatal diseases.
-They're here. -Let's go!
Everyone to the cabins!
-Gamboa, you still haven't explained to me how you survived a week...
…adrift.
-That's a transponder. -I didn't think you knew so much.
-I'm not going to let you hurt Bubble.
-He's more to blame for what happened than anyone else.
-It hurts a lot. Something's not right.
-Ah!
-The consequences of what you've done...
...they're way above you. They're way above me.
I thought you'd never be a problem again.
-I wish everything was as easy as letting go and dancing.
- Are we going to dance on the boat? - Yes.
-Don't even think about taking off your apron.
For me you're always on Sunday, blonde.
-If I could move, I'd kiss you.
-I've fallen in love with you.
-Put your butt up. (LAUGHS)
-Look how pretty she is.
-Ricardo. Ri...
-Prepare me a good penance,
because I'm going to sin on all four sides.
-I hate you and there's nothing in this world you can do...
...for that to change.
-Ah!
-Your nightmare is over. This ship is your new home...
...and all of us, his family. Welcome to the Estrella Polar.
(Applause)
-I have a message for you.