PREVIOUSLY...
I'm Ricardo Montero, and I'll be your captain.
on the training ship, the Polar Star, for the next two months.
The particle accelerator will start at 9 am in the Geneva conventions.
I don't like you.
It?
The Polar Star, speaks a training ship.
There is a growing storm coming our way.
- Are you copying? - Where is my mother?
Don't teach me how to raise my daughter.
while your son is locked in the hold.
- I came to meet my father. With The approach of the storm, is suicidal.
Each of those red dots are not part of the ship, sending the year of the SAUCE.
Turn the ship around! If we go, we all die!
No, the harbour master of the cloud, the rescue unit...
It was as if everyone had disappeared.
When you're away from home
What do you miss most in the world is in your bed.
Well, for my sisters Birthday, it's the bathroom.
She says she can only do things comfortably at home.
But after that, it's the bed.
Mom used to say, there's no place like home to sleep.
Because you have, in your dream, the sheets smell like the conditioner that you use at home
- and street noises don't wake you up.
Well, what does she look like, man? - Here.
She's beautiful! - Look, you're not afraid to go out at night.
to the kitchen to drink water.
And.
And you'll miss, lying on the carpet, too.
and turning the TV on very low,
so that Mommy doesn't wake you up and send you to bed.
This is the training ship of the Polar Star, sending out the year in the SAUCE.
Anyone out there? I can't believe no one is listening to it.
Well, you'll miss everything about the house.
There is no better place in the world.
That's why when we play tag during recess,
you'll have to say "home" to avoid getting caught.
It took me half an hour to convince him to put the ship in irons here.
- What excuse did you make up? - Not to mention the project
that we had to do biological tests in the area.
He's actually quite kind.
- Intimate. How intimate?
He saw the plush panties you gave me.
He's actually quite nice. Actually...
...to repair the broken pipe...
Sealing of the security class to fix the pipe that broke during transit.
A mistake in passing, and they moved on.
Come on.
We have an unfinished conversation. Don't you think?
In your RESUME, you say you have a phd in medicine and biology,
but you didn't say anything about traveling with it in your carry-on.
I'm so sorry about what happened. You pointed the gun at me.
I could lock you in a cabin until I hand you over to the harbor master's degree.
You knew it wasn't a normal storm.
And that we wouldn't sink if we stayed within the marked coordinates.
I think you owe me an explanation. Don't you?
THROWING THE GAME
Please.
Max.
Leave the TV on, we have to make the choice.
There is no reception offshore.
Yes, but I have an antenna and I'm always tuning into something.
Sometimes they speak Chinese, English, or other strange languages.
But the heroes of the storm
nothing. The internet doesn't work either.
I have nine friends on Facebook and I'm not there.
Well, let's make breakfast.
Also, why do you want to watch TV in Black? No reason. Come on.
Xièxie míng tian jiàn.
So they said good-bye to the news from china.
- ... tian jiàn. Don't piss me off.
Come on, Please, let's have breakfast. Quick!
Oh, Julia, I don't want it to be secret, or the cargo of mysterious ship of mine.
What's inside these boxes? A shipment of rifles, a Kalashnikov?
No, no, no, of course not. I'll explain everything to you, but I need more time.
I want you to be safe.
Ricardo.
It doesn't look good at all.
The storm knocked out the electronics of the ship, and I don't have the coverage of a satellite.
And we've fixed the two waterways in the engine room with a broom.
Captain fieruri, and continued to try to go to the Headquarters of the high Command.
What? - Nothing, nothing.
Where are we?
All night long I've mapped out the routes of the astrolabe and the compass,
and, according to my calculations, it would have to be at the front of the Lanzarotei
and I can't see the ground anywhere out there.
Good day to you.
Let me see it.
I must have done something wrong. Right here.
All of the people here did something wrong.
I must have been hit by alizée that have changed the course, and we turned back.
The graphics of the new route. What the hell are you doing?
- To me it smells like a dog in heat. You are the odor. Of course, they are.
For me, I've been burning the midnight oil earth and you, flirt with the Doctor.
I saw you hugging you at the time of the storm, and now you just came out of her room.
Ricardo, you have a 15 year old. Well...
And this isn't a school field trip. - I just had a conversation about my work.
Is that clear? Clear.
Worth it, oh, baby, I'm your daddy. What do you do?
Valeria? - Yes, I am. Hold on.
Is there something wrong with that? Worth it. Why did you lock the door?
I was just getting dressed. - Getting an early start to feel bad about.
What is this?
You've made your bed, honey? Are you made of? Well, it's just so beautiful. But the last wash, tumble,
so, you'll need to get the sheets. Oh, come on, help me out.
I don't, I don't need you, daddy. I'm not dirty.
She has a strong character for a five-year-old.
She's going to end up with the orders on a pontier. You just take the bed sheets.
But you're right. If you're not dirty, we'll clean it up.
Thus, we are going to pour more soap into the big one. All right? Come on, go get yourself some breakfast.
All right.
What should I do now?
Just change the bottom sheet.
They would be able to see the coast, about two hours ago, and you need to go from page to page.
What are we doing Anymore?
Hey, good morning, Polar Star.
It's all clear.
- Make room! - Today's schedule.
Breakfast is at 8 in the morning
At 7 in the morning, in the Canary Islands
but, well, since we're in the middle of the road at Las Palmas,
we're going to use the time of the island, 7
Breakfast is at 7 in the morning
YOUR BUSINESS AND PERSONAL
-Go on, father, it's up to us. - Check in at Las Palmas in order to repair the ship.
At 18: 30.
You have two hours to get his personal affairs.
Oh, come on! It's all clear.
Oh, come on!
Come on, you guys! - Oh, come on!
Hey, hey, hey you crazy!
- This is so beautiful. - Go on, father.
Go, go, go, father.
What was that about? What? Don't you do it?
Stop.
Hey, hey, hey, to be the daughter of the Captain, you're not that great at tying knots.
Do you know what I'm really good at it? Please, please, please.
The detection of fools on a 200-mile radius.
Hold on.
In order to have a radar gun so wide,
I don't think you're close enough?
You can get the bikini back, don't you?
Or you want to give it a shot?
The other day.
Right here.
It's hot, isn't it?
This is so beautiful!
Hey, don't touch it with your foot! - I'm not touching you!
And the spoon? I can't get to them.
The Earth shook as a zdrănător and changed its magnetic field.
That's why the utensils were zăvorit up at the sky. Don't you remember?
Because of the fact that the storm took place in the center of the Earth.
What the hell is going on here?
I don't hold it against him. I guess I thought it was funny, and it was at that age.
The ship, isn't it?
Professor of biology? - I don't. I'd like to be.
I'm a graduate student, and I'm not a biologist.
In Colombia, the brothers, who live in Barranquilla, there is no way for you to study.
Gamboa, a professor of the faculty of physical education and survival skills.
- Nice to meet you. Good to see you.
Hey, guys, did you feel that?
It's disgusting. - Duck, it ain't funny, man.
- Oh, am I? I swear it wasn't me. Come On, I Cringe.
Damn, I feel like I have something.
What is this? - It is, But what the hell is this, man?
This put a lot of! This put a lot of!
- Jenny! - The ship!
Get out of the water quickly. Quickly, come on!
Come on out, come on come on. Oh, come on!
Get out of my way. It's not going to stop touching it.
Give me your hand.
What happened to you? Let's go to the nursery.
- I need to go pee-pee on the sting. No!
I saw it in a movie, pee-pee is ammonia...
I'll cut it off, I Cringe.
That's it. You're a clown. The fool with the chewing gum.
You're going to tell the next joke, the big roof.
The fool with the chewing-gum
it is the same as on the first day, second-day,
on the third day,
in the rest of the day.
Come on, now!
- Take a seat, please! Take it to the left.
You.
Well, if you think that you have arrived on this ship, you take off your belt and a bra, then you're wrong.
Why? Are you the bully?
- Of course. - When you grow up without a father figure,
it's easy to get off track, you know?
But now that I've found you - I-you, you idiot.
If you're doing it again.
My family is my ship, and the Captain. Got it?
- This baby... hey, Hey, one more thing.
I hope you guys like cats
the cards of the game, feeding the pigeons...
For more than a couple of years ago, I can see you wearing a sweatshirt and on to the work.
People just like you.
to end up alone.
My dad.
You're the one who's going to be all alone.
But the cleaning of the fish is frozen. And I don't want to see you out on the deck.
Let's see if you're on the way to get to work and to unlock the bra.
Take out the earring.
It's a piece of advice as a father, or an order of the prime amate?
For an order. Well, I don't want to.
Lay it down. What happened to you?
Something poked me in the water.
It was like a jelly fish a jelly fish.
Yes, it was a jellyfish on the atomic scale.
Did you see how fast he had moved on? It was a shark, or something else.
I wasn't doing anything. Stand still. - A big blow.
All RIGHT.
Well, no, it's not.
It could be a flat tire.
A breakdown on some of the fish for a shed to protect you.
The swelling and sting...
- There's a poison. I got the shot wound? - I don't.
I Don't I Don't. No You Don't!
No You Don't! - Spit it out, dad.
No You Don't!
Let me see it, let's shoot some poison.
- It's the 100-mg dose of hydrocortisone. In any case, the doctor. I don't inject it.
She can suck it until I get a brain, but not cortisol.
Doctor, will you check the pulse of this, and it doesn't sting.
Tonight, the brazier with his eyes bulged. But what is it?
Don't touch it. Just leave it there and walk away.
Come out!!! Get away from him. Come on, everyone in the class.
Everyone in the class. Oh, come on! Out!!!
Out. Palomares, on the outside.
Come on, please. Out.
So, how have you been. Good morning to you.
You are here - Dad, please, please, please.
All right.
- What is it? - It's good.
With your classmates? Do you fit in? Yes, it's great.
They are really cool and you don't have to be seasick.
I'm so glad to hear you say that.
But if I find out who's got you nice to meet you, I'll squeeze in on the main-mast.
And it's not like a father, but also as a captain.
All right. I can see it now. Bye-bye.
My daughter.
Oh well, I'll wet the bed?
My mom and I pulled his diaper when he was two years old
and that's when it was wet. Why?
Until today.
Have you seen her, or did she tell you? - I don't do it. It was the other way around.
She had made her bed and covered her up so I don't see it.
- Poor thing, she must be so embarrassed. Yeah, what do I do?
- All right. I'll talk to her?
They forbid the water, at night? I put a small box on the bed, a sanitary napkin? Baby, you're my mother used to take care of these things.
My dad.
Just relax, okay?
You're doing just fine.
And Valeria is a very, very happy to be here.
It is just a child of five years old, and the five-year-olds wet their beds.
It's all right.
I don't do anything to change his bed sheets, and the...
And they act like normal. - Of course, but how?
If you pay attention, she's going to think that this is a problem.
So, the norm of the absolute.
Normal. Normal.
Come on over here.
Hey there!
Here is the flag of a pirate.
Very, very good.
You get in your bikini and you take out the garbage. We're even.
Right, smutch?
- The Snitch. Yes.
Who do you think you are?
Rip my panties and have some fun
and it's got your back. Or how does it work? - I don't know I don't like to fly.
But your father won't like to be topless on a boat.
Your father won't like that you leave empty all along the corridor.
You are so right.
Because I can't leave it on your head.
Hey, hey, hey so if you can't get rid of the smell
you call your mom and let her to give you a hand as you've had since you were a little girl.
Oh, My God.
Where are you going?
I asked you where you were going.
Take a look at me now! Where are you going?
An Idiot.
Don't even try to tell my mom, right?
You can call me whatever you want, but don't say a word about my mother.
The Snitch.
We are all fucked up.
The more you know about Jenny?
It's still in the nursery, but the doctor says he's in no immediate danger. It's stable.
Do you know what's up with that?
I don't.
Damn it, I jumped! Shut the front door. Come on over here.
What are you doing, man? - I'm a man of action.
You see, I don't want you to embarrass me.
I'm not going to do the trick siamese cat.
Don't tell me to turn the other cheek. I won't say a word to me. Don't you think that I didn't do this kind of stuff in the workshop.
They should be able to create an atmosphere for the rest of the class. It's not good.
Look at this guy, he's cocky. If you don't turn it off on the first day, he's going to humiliate you in every single day of this curse.
Wait, wait. - He is coming!
It's coming!!
Good morning. Good morning.
Well, my name is Ernesto Gamboa.
with me, you're going to, you know, what's around you.
This is how you do it,
how do you survive when things get ugly.
Damn it.
The ship, the training of the Polar Star, is calling on the Headquarters of the high Command.
Navigate without a GPS.
I need the exact location of the ship on cruise control. Over it.
- The Polar Star, her name workout - - there's No radio, TELEVISION, and the internet.
Can't find the Island. What's the deal? I don't know what it is? Just let me know.
Now, the chef knows all about the navigation?
Do you want to be in charge? - No, no, I don't.
But I'll tell you all about how she knows the chef.
On treating people nicely.
I don't like you.
Do you treat your son like he's a piece of shit.
And do you know why? In order that I might have to hate you for it you don't get the hate on anyone but yourself.
In the last 20 years we've been together, I haven't told her anything ever again. But you have to be a bitch to get off,
left her panties and dinner is on the table, and I was in there.
Today, of course.
I have no idea why I'm out of the house.
Said, you don't have it.
Well, it turns out that what I was stung was not an idiot, aren't you?
Julia, what can I do with the poison?
This wound is so much better, anti-histamine, it worked.
Check you out with your scanner to see if there is any damage to the blood vessels.
This does not have any of the risk.
All right.
- He's trying to stay calm, okay? - All right.
I don't get a move on, please.
Help! Anyone out there?
Hello.
I don't.
Can you?
It's over, Please. You can't go back now.
You're not going to die because of what he got, right?
It is a baby, the abyssal careproctus.
A fish that can live up to 5000 meters depth.
For a child who lives in the 5000 metres below the surface?
- Oh, my god, what if he is a child, so how is she to him? Large.
Large. You need to be a big thing, if it thins the child is six inches in length,
mom you have to be twenty years of age. And...
And, if that is the twenties, my mother has a 12-feet in length. Like this one.
Twelve feet tall? - More or less.
In Julia, but it's not impossible.
Sometimes, it may happen the impossible things. Sometimes, it may happen the impossible things.
Have you heard of it?
This is the area of the hull.
Help!
Anyone out there? Hello.
Anyone out there?
Do you have some muscles? It's so good.
No, seriously, girl, cheer up. We're gonna get to do it at any time.
When I shut the engine off, we're gonna get you out of here, okay? Seriously, calm down, calm down.
We're at minus 20 degrees celsius. I'll put up with no more than half an hour.
Right. But we do have a little bit of anti-freeze.
The alcohol is removed with the cold, don't you? And it makes your life more joyful, for that you will need.
Alcohol is a vasodilator.
You are going to cause you to lose heat more quickly, and you will be out of the tissues.
And, yes, the rhythm of the heart would stop bit by bit.
Why don't you get bored with the 1000 ways to die in the freezer?
Please, please, please. I'm so sorry.
Are you cold?
- I don't. - Don't you?
Your t-shirt doesn't say the exact same thing.
Oh, my god.
You're a fucking idiot. - Am I?
If you continue to jump on, all you will do is to lose calories faster.
Are you going to give me the lessons to survival?
The only clothes you're wearing are met.
Just take it off.
Her clothes are wet and you're gonna freeze to death.
Put this on.
I'm not going to forget it. I'll be back.
Right here.
Do you know how to give it to me, please? - Oh, yes, here you are.
Do you want to make a soup, bouillabaisse eyes bulged?
- The Bubble, what is it? - It's a fish.
A fish that is at least 5,000 feet.
What is he doing here? 't be able to live on the water, he burned it.
Why did he burn it?
Because people don't realize it,
for that, I don't know, but the sea is 6 degrees warmer.
Why is it so?
For the same reason, and with a knife and fork, because the Earth is shaking
and the lava that came out of the bottom of the sea.
You have to be out a lot of the lava, to heat up the whole of the ocean.
Oh well, I'll leave it here.
- For the Home. We can't be in the National Park of picos de europa.
- Out of the building. - ¿Qué?
Why? My daughter is in the cabin shy
for that, you hung up the sheets from the boom to the spots of pee and all that stuff.
Leave them out on the bed, it is difficult to remove the smell.
They can stay up there till the moss grows.
The ship is telling me that I need to normalize things and you'll be humiliated.
Give him the ears of an ass, and a walk to the bridge for the world to laugh!
Damn it, he's five years old.
I'm so sorry. I don't know, I just do it without thinking about it.
Ricardo, don't worry about it. Also, I'm going to normalize things up the next time you see her.
We are a family. I'm her uncle.
I need to learn how to deal with a child of five years old.
I can teach you. You can find his son after 20 years of age and to turn it off.
You're a sick man, Julian. Sick!
You're a sick man, uncle Julian? What's the matter with you?
No, it's nothing, baby. It is not sick. Uncle Julian is not.
Your dad was mad at me.
'Cause I wet the bed again.
Are you-are you serious?
Yes, my dear. And you know what?
It turns out that, along with the sound of the waves is my turn on the tap and you're done! I get wet every night. As an old mule.
I don't even have pajamas.
In the box, the number 23, you will find the whole of the protocol of action
in the event of an accident.
Start the protocol of action in the event of a disaster.
In fact, it is possible for an accident to the launch of a particle accelerator
he went up to the consequences of the proportions of the immeasurable.
The safest assumption is that it was generated by a black hole
and took about 500 cubic kilometres-of mass frame.
If this is the case,
The earth is positively different.
Do you know that the first step of the protocol is to assess the situation. In this case, the number 23, you'll find a receiver of a satellite image.
Hispasat 14 will be broadcast every hour.
You'll be able to check the extent to which the planet has been devastated.
And the good thing about all of this ...
it's you and me, we're not going to stop fighting in order to live in Valencia or the Geneva convention. I'm guessing that you don't get to see this footage, but just in case, I want you to know
I love you, too.
And I will always love you.
It's like the first day.
at the University.
If decompression is not performed correctly,the
the bubbles of nitrogen gas could increase by as much as four times their file size in the blood
leaving the diver, unconscious.
What do we do in this case?
- Doesn't show up? - Let's go into a hyperbaric chamber?
That's just great.
but, let me remind you that at times, the chamber is miles away, you
and then you float away with the body.
So, the first thing you have to do is to draw a scuba diver on the launch pad.
I always have to get the person to get hurt in the back,
leaning against him, against our own.
What are you doing here? What do you hear?
Nothing. I already knew that.
Ce știai?
Trebuie să fii foarte prost să nu realizezi că planeta este pe jumătate devastată.
Televiziunea chinezească nu funcționează, iar televiziunea chinezească funcționează întotdeauna.
Știi ce?
Am nevoie de un asistent pe navă.
Bine.
Spatele lui va fi bine pe corpul nostru,
astfel încât să putem să-i închidem cutia toracică în brațul nostru
și eliberați astfel căile respiratorii. Foarte important.
Și, în acest fel, atragem scafandru la lansare
înot înapoi, evident.
- Alte întrebări? - Scuzați-mă, domnule Gamboa.
Să presupunem că persoana rănită este o femeie cu sânii mari,
de unde îi ținem cutia toracică? De sus, de jos...?
Nu sunt serios.
Ştii? M-am întrebat acelaşi lucru,
dar manualele de supraviețuire nu acordă atenție siliconului.
Ei bine, atunci hai să continuăm cu lecția.
We can't continue on with the lesson.
Well, there are two types of cardiac arrest.
Well, I'm-I'm sorry, class is over. Thank you.
You can hang out with all of you. Except for you.
You might be interested in doing a little bit of work for me.
What do you think?
What can I say?
Work demnește the man.
I am already worn out through the urine.
- You tie it to the boom, right away. Listen to me.
What the hell are you doing?
The normalization of the things in hell.
And accepting the fact that my mattress is so dry that it looks like a rice field.
Uncle Julian spends his nights, drowned, soaking wet...
Come in.
The captain.
I need to talk to you. I can't see you to your cabin?
All right.
Worth it, baby, why don't you just ask Julian, and in addition to, take it to the bridge. Learn how to tie knots, right? Oh, come on. I'll see you later, babe.
Uncle Julian,
is it okay to wet the bed, but that's only sometimes.
Don't worry about it, the first mate, I'll get you a pot for your room.
Go ahead, Please.
But you don't, you can't use your brains?
Right now, my daughter, he sees the usual wet bed sheets up to 40 years of age.
- It normalizes it for you? The girl left her happy.
Don't worry about it. Easy, we grow it, how it should be.
You're not, you're not her mother. The doctor is her mother?
Ricardo, get wet ...
because this is a night all alone to jerk off to that.
Both of them speak in a low voice, while his daughter is in front of you.
And what's worse, you take off out of respect for the memory of Marisa.
Do you want me to put my hands under your shirt?
We can't keep up the heat together in this way.
Just...
Just like that? No movies, no date,...
You're such a jerk.
We're all frozen to death.
Or are you ashamed? - I don't.
Come on, then. Done.
All right.
Right.
- Twitch. What? How would I be able to shake?
I can handle very well with the cold. I've been through so much the cold.
Maybe you need to give me a hug, and for me to keep up the heat for as long as possible, isn't it?
I'm so sorry.
You may ask yourself, why do I punish you, only you, and those two fools have your
the little priest, and the one with the limp.
I don't know. To be alone with me?
- You're a friend to the archbishop of Boston? - I don't.
For the wolf pack's next the dominant
and, if you're done with it, and the rest disappears.
It's only fair. I've seen it in a documentary. That's right, yeah.
I haven't been able to finish a lesson from your account. Do you want to hear the end of it?
Yes, yes, yes, yes, please.
The...
sleep apnea, or dive in apnea is a suspension of the voluntary into the water.
When it is lacking oxygen, the body responds to the compression of the diaphragm,
since there is an increase in CO2 in the blood.
Which is why a lot of people don't know is that she's left enough of the oxygen in our body.
let's continue with a little bit.
What's the deal? - Can I touch your breast, your Child.
- I'm a girl. You are you.
I'm not. You are you.
I'm just trying to stick my hand in my armpit. - Of course.
It keeps very well with the heat. Don't you know that?
Please correct the course of about 30 degrees, and a body count, because they're on the wrong track.
In addition to that, you're not my type.
I think you're just too cool. - Am I?
No, you're not my kind of thing.
- Don't you? - I don't.
And who do you love?
Someone else on the ship.
The handsome middle of the afternoon.
No way. I don't fuck with me. Why don't you?
After the contraction, there is a feeling of warmth.
I don't pay attention, I can't stand it.
How do you like a guy who is waiting for the squat to put a bath robe?
I've seen it.
I think it's so sexy to me.
In addition, he is a professor of survival.
And I'm not sure if I would have been locked up with him, he would be out a long time ago.
I like to go out with.
Take your clothes off.
What? Take your clothes off. You're not going to stop until I get to see you naked.
- Do you want me to take it? - You're not.
I need to know who you are,
do you know the environment in which you move in.
You're wrong about me, kid.
Because, in the ocean, I'm the big one.
Hey, Hey, Hey Gamboa. What do you do?
Hey! Good, and you?
What's the deal? What's the deal? I've got some company.
What's the matter with you?
You with me? Nothing. You with anything?
I saw you take the antacid at the wrong time in 15 years
and you do it only when you are in trouble.
I'll do it for you. What's the matter with you?
Nothing.
At Home. The place to find the course that makes me wake up.
Oh, Doctor? Yes, that's right.
He says, why don't you slip, I'm sleeping in her room.
I was flirting with her.
Do you know what is the matter with you?
He's the jealous type.
- About what? - About what? He's the jealous type.
Marisa, this is your wife at home. Julian, it's your wife on the ship.
- And all of a sudden, and harmony. - Together?
I don't care about the Doctor.
I don't want to start over or something. The end of the story.
Ricardo, in his Captain's telling me all this?
Ricardo.
Well, in the first place.
You know, Marisa was like a sister to me.
And she's not here, you are too.
If you do decide to take it out of the way, I don't think you're cheating on her.
And second of all, Julian is the one, that of a dog abandoned,
and it is up to you.
It would take the ship to the reef, just to get your attention.
Just take it. I made it with love, with love.
From what I can tell you about the fish that big?
Well...
I can't tell you because...
Because it will be our little secret.
I understand.
Why do we keep secrets?
For that, there are things that...
Because the rest you don't need to know that...
I can't hurt you. Do you understand? - I do.
Where is the antacid?
The antacid... it's in front of your very eyes.
What's the deal? Hey - hey-hey.
What's the situation.
What is the situation for the rest of the world. Well, I'll leave you two to your business.
CONNECTING A SATELLITE
THE CONNECTION WITH THE SATELLITE HISPASAT 14 VIEWS: THE WESTERN PART OF THE EARTH
START THE DOWNLOAD
You Don Ricardo's...
Just let me know. - No, you go first.
Don't tell me. Why?
It can...
they have become a bit blind to the Doctor. No, not at all. I don't have blind at all.
In fact, I've opened up my eyes.
I've done it? Yes.
The first thing I did was to talk to her, and...
I've cleared things up.
Well...
And how did he take it? CONNECTION ERROR
It was a bit of a disappointment.
Well, that's how I was crying like a crazy person.
She'll get over it.
Do you want to go to see it. No I Don't.
I would rather think about other things. - All right.
Why don't you go on the fishing trip, like always.
Oh, come on.
- Oh, yeah? - Shall we?
Hey - hey-hey. I don't eat it for dinner? Stop by for dinner, dad.
Gamboa had been trying to drown it in a dish washing machine. I can barely alive.
Do you have a grudge against the teacher, and you want it to be us.
What grudges?
I swear to God
I would keep it out of my head and it won't let me breathe.
That guy was crazy, really. - You are under arrest.
We'll report back about what happened.
We're gonna go to what's right in court, if necessary.
But, if you put your head in a bucket, I swear to god I will kick you out. How do we do that? It's his word against mine.
A word from the teacher, against your asshole with a stick of gum.
Do you think I will believe you? - What do you think you're talking to him?
Maybe it was all a misunderstanding. I would hire a teacher so paranoid.
- Get yourself in his dressing room, ask for an explanation. - What is your explanation? Huh?
You need to make your crazy is that crazy to come clean.
What are the chances that you get it right?
The ship is made of wood.
And the regulations provide that there must be a smoke detector in each of the 5 ft.
And there's another one over here.
The only chance we have is to make it to the alarm of the bridge,
because there's always someone out there for you, okay?
And if you don't hear it? If this doesn't work?
Well, if you don't hear us, instead of freezing to death,
we're going to die of suffocation, because there is no grid air vent.
We can try it.
Oh, come on.
My fingers are frozen.
It's slippery.
I... I ... I can't. I can't.
I can't. - All right.
All right. Calm down. Give me that.
Give me your hands, give it to me.
- The more the better? - Freeze.
I guess I can just feel it.
All right.
We believe that it is impossible to get a fire going in the freezer.
Sometimes things happen to you is impossible.
If it doesn't work well, at least we're going to be spending a great night, don't you?
Yes.
But for me, it's so cold.
I'm so cold. - Come here.
I don't see any light. If there is no light, there is no coastline.
Corrected to 15 degrees.
Set your course for the north Star.
Just let them off the canvas. Slow down.
The bridge was burned.
What do you do? - Fine.
It is so swollen and hurt so much.
I'm so glad to hear you say that. If you're in need of something.
Do you know where the Captain is? - I don't.
Julia.
Aren't you going to ask me a question about anything?
Aren't you going to tell me that it's madness to go to the board when you're pregnant?
I'm...
Oh, yeah, I'm not going to tell you something.
I don't know if you know this, how certain are you that you're a mother at your age
but the baby is much more important than you might think.
This baby is the most...
The most important thing in the world.
And I need you to take care of it.
No, no, we're not going to fit in there.
It's not a place.
But-but - what's this guy's got three passports.
Mexico...
In mexico, Cuba and Hungary.
I don't know. Maybe it's the best.
But he does have three different identities.
- There is no signal. - It is not possible, Please.
The satellite is still up there. - It is.
But the antenna all the way down here I'm not there. And what if the dishes are not there
there is no signal. I understand.
And what are the feelers out there, Please?
Do you know why, don't you?
Bubble, hey, look at me.
Don't you tell Her?
I don't.
Because it is not a secret.
I'll answer the door, he said, is that if people know that there are...
in an accident, and that all the land was gone, and that he would hurt her.
Do you know what it is, is a particle accelerator?
Are you sad right now?
I don't.
I'm not sad.
I'm happy.
it's you and me, are we alive.
I've always hovered on the ship.
This is our home.
Come along with Her.
What the hell! This guy could be a serial killer, a psychopath, he's a drug dealer,
while the search in his bag.
Good night.
- Come on, come on come on. In the dressing room. But what is it?
'Cause I'm a fool, and thou art a priest.
Can you please tell me what are you doing here?
I've come to the...
... in order to ask for an apology.
Come on in.
- Captain. What happened to you?
It has been a disaster.
Just wait for me here.
I'll be right back.
Where did he sound the alarm? - During the bridge of the engine.
I'm coming!
I don't have my phone. Put it on your own.
Ricardo, are you coming?
I've seen a ton of great.
Is anyone in here? - Dad!
Dad!!! Dad!!!
Don't worry, honey. Just stay calm.
Get out there and put out the fire now.
Carlos, you go get some towels for you.
Dear, dear, are you all right?
Are you all right, darling?
It's over. You're freezing.
It was all my fault. I walked in and I forgot to latch the door.
I Accept all responsibility for taxes, cap.
It's not my fault. - I'm pretty sure that was it.
Honey.
What are you doing here?
Oh,come on,
go to Her, I'll make you a bowl of soup.
Be careful.
Don't worry about it, captain. Calm down, there's nothing wrong with it.
In addition to that, the things of your daughter, and I'm still a little bit cold.
Stay away from my daughter.
I've heard over the walkie-talkie. What happened to you?
Nothing, just a small fire. It's all worked out. Don't worry about it.
You didn't bring your fishing line?
I don't.
Here, Julian.
I'm just delaying the inevitable for months and months, but...
Why?
You were right about that ship, and the family does not go well together.
So...
I have to leave the ship.
The Camera. Come on, turn it on.
I know that we all make mistakes, don't you?
That's why I'm giving you a chance to ask for a formal apology
before the facts are known. Are you threatening me, boy?
What would come to be known, exactly?
I stayed after class to go over the lesson.
- Oh, come on. Wait.
Done.
All right.
Or are you looking for a tutor?
What would come to be known it's you, you, you slipped into my room.
The memory is full.
I need to get out of things.
You can see the nervous boy.
It is possible that you may need to drink more water. I don't want anything?
Oh, come on.
I don't fuck with me Anymore.
Take a scotch tape, aspirin, go to bed.
And don't be stupid. - No, no, you're a sailor, but I'm a father.
Julian and I am a very selfish thing I brought my daughters here.
I want you to wait up so the Ship let's go back to disco
and you can see the tooth fairy when she's coming after your teeth, Valerie.
Here may be a fairy on the tooth. I went too far.
- You are in there, that's all... no, No, Julian, that's...
In today's crash of a pee-pee yet, but tomorrow will be a period of time,
the next day, the first of a lipstick, and the first love of the Ainhoei.
I don't belong to them, Julian.
Will you do me a favor and drive the Polaris 20 years of age?
I don't fuck with me, man.
If I go with you?
You've got your son is here.
Oh, yeah, I don't.
You have to delete the photos from my mother?
Give it to me.
Captain, you might be interested to know that you've got three passports.
Do not delete it.
I can see that you don't have to tell all your friends who's the big fish in the ocean.
Oh, man, you are a deranged psychopath
and I would have to turn himself in. I'll report back.
No, no, no I don't report anything on here.
I'm giving you two options.
One, you get down to do it and get out.
If you have the courage to stay here, be careful
'cause tonight,
tomorrow or any other night
the three idiots are falling in the water geamandă and no one ever finds it.
And the three of them:
You're the one who's gonna get on the boat, and you will be gone.
Once you arrive at the port, your journey is over, the Gamboa.
You will report to the right authorities of the port concerned.
Please, I'm waiting for you.
It's very, very important. I need to talk to you.
So, if you don't, he's left this earth, there is no Facebook.
If there are no Facebook...
I'm not going to be friends. Do you have any friends that already.
We have a captain,
you've got me,
you've got all the new guys.
And I think we're gonna have plenty of time to get to know each other.
But we can't do anything.
We can make a new Facebook.
There isn't anything right now, so that we can make it whatever you want.
What do you think?
I want to invent the internet.
And Coca-Cola. I want you to make up a Coca-Cola!
Captain, you're bleeding.
Yes, it's no problem. Just a place where I scraped it. Listen to me carefully.
- Captain. I'm going to start a life on the land with my children.
- I don't. I don't want to lose what we have.
This is not So...
- Open it Anymore, and I'm... now I'm no longer a captain.
- Ricardo-open. Listen to me.
I can hear you, damn it. I have to tell you something very important.
What is the most important thing that you have to say?
You've wet the bed again?
I'm so sorry.
The captain.
What I'm trying to say is that the storm could not have been an accident of weather,
it was all a mistake
the consequences of the geological return.
Let's make a list of all the things that you need to come up with.
The continents are in the water.
The zoo with all the animals.
There may be islands.
The candies.
... atolls, or nothing at all.
This is the west side of the planet right now. The signal was turned off when we are going to look at the other side.
Songs.
The people?
What does this mean?
I can't make it up, people.
I don't.
I can't make it up the people, the Land.
It is very likely that...
we're the only people in the world at this point in time.
I can't.
What is this?
What's going on here?
I can't take jokes or any of that crap right now.
- Look at it! - It is a kind of high-risk. Things are changing down here.
If it suffers a hemorrhage, a child should be able to die, and so was she.
I like it a lot doesn't show up,
so, I don't ask you to miss out on this opportunity.
You accept the Captain's daughter, an encounter with the bad guy?
Forget about it!
In the name of God, I beg you to get us out of the woods!
Do you have a date with a guy? On board the ship?
Julian's, just leave it at that.
Do you think the story of the black hole? Don't you?
I believe in what I see.